{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866875400","data":{"timestamp":" 946866875400"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866886083","data":{"timestamp":" 946866886083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866896116","data":{"timestamp":" 946866896116"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866902422","data":{"timestamp":" 946866902422"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866910206","data":{"timestamp":" 946866910206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866919968","data":{"timestamp":" 946866919967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866930619","data":{"timestamp":" 946866930619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866944617","data":{"timestamp":" 946866944616"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866951948","data":{"timestamp":" 946866951948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866964948","data":{"timestamp":" 946866964948"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866972262","data":{"timestamp":" 946866972262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866985307","data":{"timestamp":" 946866985307"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946866998750","data":{"timestamp":" 946866998750"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867009636","data":{"timestamp":" 946867009636"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867020517","data":{"timestamp":" 946867020517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867027247","data":{"timestamp":" 946867027247"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867038081","data":{"timestamp":" 946867038081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867045663","data":{"timestamp":" 946867045663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867057738","data":{"timestamp":" 946867057738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867066944","data":{"timestamp":" 946867066944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867075369","data":{"timestamp":" 946867075369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867085135","data":{"timestamp":" 946867085135"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867098169","data":{"timestamp":" 946867098169"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867113211","data":{"timestamp":" 946867113211"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867121619","data":{"timestamp":" 946867121618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867128674","data":{"timestamp":" 946867128674"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867136860","data":{"timestamp":" 946867136860"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867141651","data":{"timestamp":" 946867141651"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867150342","data":{"timestamp":" 946867150341"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867164663","data":{"timestamp":" 946867164663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867175897","data":{"timestamp":" 946867175897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867187084","data":{"timestamp":" 946867187084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867191379","data":{"timestamp":" 946867191379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867209255","data":{"timestamp":" 946867209255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867215435","data":{"timestamp":" 946867215435"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867224121","data":{"timestamp":" 946867224120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867228379","data":{"timestamp":" 946867228379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867234676","data":{"timestamp":" 946867234676"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867243119","data":{"timestamp":" 946867243119"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867259623","data":{"timestamp":" 946867259623"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867272143","data":{"timestamp":" 946867272143"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867281182","data":{"timestamp":" 946867281182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867290892","data":{"timestamp":" 946867290892"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867297242","data":{"timestamp":" 946867297242"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867309032","data":{"timestamp":" 946867309031"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867311732","data":{"timestamp":" 946867311732"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.19","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867325206","data":{"timestamp":" 946867325205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 68996d62-9049-40cd-a9b8-cf3a1061dffc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.19"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867342480","data":{"timestamp":" 946867342479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" c9f69e3b-12f9-40a4-adba-35e3a51a6c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867343119","data":{"timestamp":" 946867343118"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" c9f69e3b-12f9-40a4-adba-35e3a51a6c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867343374","data":{"timestamp":" 946867343373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" c9f69e3b-12f9-40a4-adba-35e3a51a6c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867343945","data":{"timestamp":" 946867343944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" c9f69e3b-12f9-40a4-adba-35e3a51a6c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867345041","data":{"timestamp":" 946867345041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" c9f69e3b-12f9-40a4-adba-35e3a51a6c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867345140","data":{"timestamp":" 946867345140"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" c9f69e3b-12f9-40a4-adba-35e3a51a6c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867387842","data":{"timestamp":" 946867387841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" c9f69e3b-12f9-40a4-adba-35e3a51a6c7b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867425346","data":{"timestamp":" 946867425346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867434089","data":{"timestamp":" 946867434089"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867441977","data":{"timestamp":" 946867441977"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867449360","data":{"timestamp":" 946867449359"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867454591","data":{"timestamp":" 946867454591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867462766","data":{"timestamp":" 946867462766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867470255","data":{"timestamp":" 946867470255"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" +"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867485127","data":{"timestamp":" 946867485127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867501699","data":{"timestamp":" 946867501699"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867512507","data":{"timestamp":" 946867512507"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867523776","data":{"timestamp":" 946867523775"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867529574","data":{"timestamp":" 946867529574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867537051","data":{"timestamp":" 946867537051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867541362","data":{"timestamp":" 946867541362"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867558309","data":{"timestamp":" 946867558308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867564488","data":{"timestamp":" 946867564487"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867574020","data":{"timestamp":" 946867574020"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867580555","data":{"timestamp":" 946867580555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867596268","data":{"timestamp":" 946867596268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867606301","data":{"timestamp":" 946867606301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867613397","data":{"timestamp":" 946867613397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867627795","data":{"timestamp":" 946867627795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867641184","data":{"timestamp":" 946867641184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867650212","data":{"timestamp":" 946867650212"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867656006","data":{"timestamp":" 946867656006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867665793","data":{"timestamp":" 946867665793"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867680805","data":{"timestamp":" 946867680805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867695671","data":{"timestamp":" 946867695671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867705117","data":{"timestamp":" 946867705117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867713657","data":{"timestamp":" 946867713656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867728523","data":{"timestamp":" 946867728522"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867737806","data":{"timestamp":" 946867737806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867751829","data":{"timestamp":" 946867751829"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867764041","data":{"timestamp":" 946867764041"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867772547","data":{"timestamp":" 946867772547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867793671","data":{"timestamp":" 946867793671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867798346","data":{"timestamp":" 946867798346"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867808685","data":{"timestamp":" 946867808685"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867817312","data":{"timestamp":" 946867817312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_METRIC - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867827195","data":{"timestamp":" 946867827194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867837017","data":{"timestamp":" 946867837017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867842559","data":{"timestamp":" 946867842559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867853049","data":{"timestamp":" 946867853049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ka.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946867867997","data":{"timestamp":" 946867867997"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000103_053404"," gameId":" 59e60d49-1185-4d29-bc6f-4d6249d71451"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ka.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ka__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}